Mss.Rec.138 Mss.Rec.138
American Philosophical Society
- Indian Summer School Dance Program. Various Tribes. New Mexico., June 28, 1950; Mss.Rec.138.10; 5.0 Reel(s)
  - Announcements and Jokes, 1950-06-28; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:09; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
  - Navaho Yebichai, 1950-06-28; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:46; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
  - Navaho Love Songs, 1950-06-28; 03-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:24; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
    Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Love songs; Navajo Indians--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.)
  - Hopi Buffalo Dance of Keames Cañon, 1950-06-28; 03-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:15:47; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
    Hopi dance; Hopi Indians--Music; Hopi Indians--Social life and customs; Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.)
  - San Carlos Apache Sunrise Dance, 1950-06-28; 03-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:46; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
    Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.); Sun--Rising and setting--Songs and music; Western Apache dance; Western Apache Indians--Music
  - Navaho Feather Dance, 1950-06-28; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:33; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005
    Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Navajo dance; Navajo Indians--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.)
  - Taos Dancers - War Dance, 1950-06-28; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:18; Concha, Eliseo; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
    Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.); Taos dance; Taos Indians--Music
  - Horse Tail Dance, 1950-06-28; 04-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:31; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
  - Hoop Dance, 1950-06-28; 04-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:30; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
  - Circle Dance, 1950-06-28; 04-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:08:15; Concha, Eliseo; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005
  - Jemez Eagle Dance, 1950-06-28; 04-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:31; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
    Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Jemez dance; Jemez Indians--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.)
  - Navaho Feather Dance, 1950-06-28; 04-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:51; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
  - Zuni Sunrise Song, 1950-06-28; 04-08; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:47; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George; War Bow
    Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.); Sun--Rising and setting--Songs and music; Zuni Indians--Music
  - The land of the sky-blue water, 1950-06-28; 04-09; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:45; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George; War Bow
    Indians of North America--New Mexico--Music; Powwows--New Mexico; Santa Fe (N.M.)
  - Comments from M.C., 1950-06-28; 04-10; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:16; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
  - Acknowledgements, Indian Jokes, 1950-06-28; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:10:45; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Smith, George
- Seneca Songs and Dances, recorded by Dorothy Shipley Gaus, 1962; Mss.Rec.138.11; 13.0 Reel(s)
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2605, 1962-07-25; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:30:21; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-; Jimerson, Avery; Johnny John, Richard; Preston, Jack
    Consists of 17 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2606, 1962; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:18:16; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-; Jimerson, Avery; Johnny John, Richard; Preston, Jack
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2607, 1962; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:33:52; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-
    Consists of 30 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2608, 1962; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:10:01; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-; Johnson, Danny
    Consists of 10 individual programs. The final program is an "Eskimo Dance," performed by Danny Johnson. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2609, 1962-08-05; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:23:38; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-
    Consists of 3 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2610, 1962; 06-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:11:04; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-
    Consists of 13 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2611, 1962-08-06; 07-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:23:16; Curry, Ed; Dowdy, Herb; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-; Jimerson, Avery; Johns, Albert; Redeye, Nelson
    Singing session at Avery Jimerson's, and Fish Dances. Consists of 21 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2612, 1962-08-09; 08-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:28:53; Dowdy, Herb; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-
    Consists of 7 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2613, 1962-08; 09-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:14:20; Dowdy, Herb; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-; Jimerson, Danny
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2614, 1962; 10-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:31:12; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-
    Consists of 9 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2615, 1962-08-11; 11-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:30:57; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-
    Consists of 4 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2616, 1962; 12-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:20:57; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-
    Consists of 21 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
  - Seneca, Allegany Reservation, Harrell 1963, tape 2617, 1962-08-22; 13-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:20:06; Fenton, William N., (William Nelson), 1908-2005; Gaus, Dorothy Shipley, 1928-; Jimerson, Lester
    Consists of 16 individual programs. This is a duplicate of an original tape deposited by Dorothy Shipley Gaus at the Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.